God, you're beautiful.
Why are we fighting this?
You know you want it to happen
as much as I do.
I want you. I need you.
Let me make love to you.
I don't wanna stand in the way
of true love or anything..
but I think a cantaloupe
might hurt less.
No, I'm rehearsing my lines.
They're giving me a romantic story
on Days of Our Lives.
It's the first time my character's gotten one.
I'm nervous. I want it to be good.
I haven't seen you this worked-up since
you did that dog-food commercial..
and you thought you were gonna be
with a real talking dog.
Yeah, that was a disappointment.
You wanna come down to the set
and tell me if I'm doing okay?
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
You just have to promise not
to get thrown out again.
- That was an honest mistake.
- Right.
"Oh, my God. Is this the men's room?
I feel so foolish.
Have you always known
you wanted to be an actor?"
Yeah, that was an awesome day.
- Hey.
You guys wanna come eat dinner
at the restaurant in the next few weeks?
- I'd love to.
- Well, you can't.
- We're booked solid for the next month.
- Well, I can't give you a massage..
because my license
has been revoked again.
- Phoebe, what happened?
- Well, it was an accident, you know.
It's a lot of oil and sometimes
the hand just slips.
So the restaurant's doing well, you say?
It is so great. There are people
lining up in the street..
to taste my food. Saturday,
there's a waiting list of 50 people.
I know how that feels.
Last semester, I had two students..
who wanted to take my 1:00 class,
but it was full.
So they had to take my 5:00.
That's not the same.
Have I got a surprise for you.
Pack your bags.
Oh, no. You guys aren't supposed
to get divorced for seven years.
What? No, I'm taking Monica
to a romantic inn in Vermont.
Oh, good. Okay, good for you.
Trying to recapture the magic.
- So can you get out of work?
- Honey, I can't.
- Things are crazy at the restaurant.
- You're really that busy?
Yeah. I'm sorry, I really am.
That's okay. I'll just try and reschedule.
Hi, this is Chandler Bing.
I made a reservation there..
and I need to change it.
What do you mean, it's nonrefundable?
Well, can I just come some other time?
Can't you make an exception?
Tell them I'm a chef
at a big New York restaurant.
Tell them that in two weeks, I will once
again be a masseuse in good standing.
Look, this is ridiculous.
I'm not paying for that room, okay?
Well, thank you very much.
Yeah, I'm going to Vermont.
- Don't worry, use your travel insurance.
- I don't have travel insurance.
Well, this is what happens
when people live on the edge.
- Honey, what are you gonna do?
- I'll go.
Okay, I'll pick you up at 10.
Oh, go with you?
Oh, I can't go.
Why don't you take Ross?
Don't you think that'll be a little weird?
I mean, two guys in a romantic inn?
- No, not if the room has two beds.
- I guess.
It still seems a little..
"Moonlight boat ride"?!
Joey, is this the bed
where Olivia lost her virginity?
I don't know,
but one of the extras sure did.
Listen, Rach. Thanks again
for coming down to watch my scenes.
Please, honey. Just the fact that you
want me here to support you, I'm..
Oh, my God. Is that Christian Saunders?
He is so gorgeous!
And also, so gay.
Well, in my head,
he's done some pretty not-gay stuff.
Well, at the Christmas party, him
and Santa did some definitely-gay stuff.
Joey? Joey, we're ready for you.
Okay. All right, wish me luck.
Okay. Not that you need it, but good..
God! Is that Chase Lassiter?
- He's straight, right?
- Rach, if you weren't here wondering..
if these guys were gay,
I don't know if I could do this.
I'm sorry, you're right.
I'm sorry. Good luck.
On a bell, please. Quietly.
And action!
Drake, what are you doing here?
Stopping you from marrying
the wrong man..
and making the biggest
mistake of your life.
- Get out.
- You don't love him.
What do you know about love?
I know what I felt that night
when we kissed under the bridge.
- That kiss never happened.
- Well, what about this one?
Now, I told you to get out.
Fine, I'll go.
But let me ask you one question.
- You look real familiar. Have we..?
- Shh! He's asking her a question.
Can you live the rest of your life never
knowing what we could have been?
- I don't have a choice.
- Yes, you do.
Yes, you do. I'm the one who doesn't
have a choice because I..
Because I can't stop loving you.
- Don't say that.
- Tell me to stop.
Just..
tell me to stop.
- Cut!
- No!
Or, cut. You know, that's your call.
- Everything was delicious.
- Thank you.
It was. The duck in particular
was superb.
Thank you.
You haven't said anything.
Actually, I do have one small complaint.
Well, please, I welcome criticism.
The musician right outside the restaurant
is kind of a mood killer.
What musician?
What are you doing here?
You said you had customers lined up
in the street, so I'm here to entertain.
- Great.
- Yeah, it really has been great too.
They must have seen me
play before..
because they requested
a bunch of my songs.
Yeah, "You Suck"..
and "Shut Up and Go Home."
Listen, Phoebe. You know how much
I love listening to your music..
- but..
- But what?
This is kind of a classy place.
Okay, say no more.
Everyone!
Classy, huh?
Hi, Chandler Bing. I have a reservation.
Welcome to the Chestnut lnn.
Where are you joining us from?
- New York.
- The Big Apple.
He's wound up. We had to stop at every
maple-candy stand on the way here.
I ate all my gifts for everybody.
I'm sorry, there's no record
of your reservation in the computer.
- That's impossible. Check again, please.
- Check again, please.
- I'm sorry, it's not here.
- It's not there.
Let me get this straight. I called
to try to cancel my reservation..
was told it's not refundable. Then we
drove six hours all the way up here..
- and now we don't have a reservation?
- I don't know what to say.
She doesn't know what to say.
Just give us
the cheapest room you have.
The only thing we have available
is our deluxe suite. The rate is $600.
- That's insane.
- It's totally insane.
Dude, let's drive home. We'll hit all the
maple-candy stores on the way back..
and if they're closed, then maybe we'll
tap a tree and make some ourselves.
Does that room have a closet
I can lock him in?
- We'll take it.
- Great.
They are totally ripping us off!
Three hundred dollars each?
"Each?" I'm your date.
So I pay for everything
and have no sex.
Oh, life before Monica.
Dude, don't worry about it.
I know how to make your money back.
This is a nice hotel. Plenty of amenities.
We just load up on those.
Like those apples. Instead of taking one..
I take six.
Great. At $100 an apple, we're there.
Come on, you get the idea. You know,
we'll make our money back in no time.
- Dude, you're shaking.
- It's the sugar. Could you hold the apple?
- Hi.
- Hey.
Joey, I gotta tell you, I have been
thinking all day about that scene you did.
I mean, you were amazing.
You know, the writing was good.
And the director's good.
And my costar's good.
But they're not as good as me!
You have to tell me
what happens tomorrow.
I'm going over the script now.
Wanna read lines with me?
Me? Oh, I'm not an actress.
- All right, I can ask Monica.
- Screw her! That part is mine!
Okay, so just from the top
of the page right here.
Okay.
Hello, Drake.
I'm surprised to see you here.
- I can't believe you married him.
- Well, what choice did I have?
He was keeping my sister in a dungeon.
So, what about us?
Everything we feel for each other?
It's over. You have to accept that.
How can I, knowing I'll never
hold you in my arms again..
or touch your skin or feel your lips..
knowing I'll never make love to you?
How can I accept
that I can never kiss you again..
when it's all I can do
not to kiss you right now?
Kiss me.
What?
- Rach, it doesn't say that.
- No, I'm saying it.
- But..
- Just don't talk.
Well, that's new.
Hi, this is Ross Geller in suite 206.
I've forgotten a couple of things.
Could you have some complimentary
toiletries sent up to my room?
Thank you.
Okay, a toothbrush, toothpaste..
razor, mouthwash, deodorant, floss,
Band-Aids, shaving cream, after-shave.
And I feel like I'm forgetting something.
Is there anything else you have
that I haven't asked for already?
Yeah, go ahead,
send up some tampons.
- What'd you get?
- USA Today.
Nice. Put it with the others.
And I also got two more apples.
We're four short of a bushel!
God, I feel so alive.
I love being in the country!
Also, got these great
salt and pepper shakers..
- from the restaurant.
- That's not cool.
Dude, none of this is cool.
Look, Chandler, you have to find
the line between stealing..
and taking what the hotel owes you.
For example: A hair dryer, no, no.
But shampoos and conditioners,
yes, yes.
Now, the salt shaker is off limits.
But the salt..
I wish I'd thought this through.
I think I get what you mean, though.
Like, the lamp is the hotel's..
but the bulbs..
Oh, you already got that.
Not my first time in a hotel, my friend.
- Okay, how about this?
- No, no, no.
- You can't take the remote control.
- Yes, but the batteries.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
- Let's celebrate with some maple candy.
- No!
At least tell me where you hid it.
- Can I ask you a question?
- Yeah.
Have you ever had any..
weird, romantic dreams?
Let me think.
When I was younger, I used to dream
that I got married to Mayor McCheese.
And on our wedding night,
I ate his head.
Okay.
Well, this is like that..
in no way.
I had a dream last night
that I wanted to kiss Joey.
Wow! You mean like
"kiss him" kiss him?
Oh, yeah.
I mean, it was pretty intense.
- What brought that on?
- I don't know.
Maybe it had to do with the fact
I saw him do a love scene.
- A love scene? With who?
- Olivia.
Olivia?! I thought she was
marrying Connor?!
Oh, right. Real life more important.
- You think my dream means anything?
- I don't know.
I mean, you saw him do a love scene.
So maybe you don't have a thing for Joey.
Maybe you have a thing for Drake.
Well, it was Joey reading
Drake's lines in the dream.
Of course it was. Trust me,
when it comes to psychology..
I know what I'm talking about.
I took two psych classes in college.
You took the same class twice.
- It was hard!
- I know.
- Hey.
- Hi, Phoebe.
Here, Monica, look what I got to wear
when I play at your restaurant.
Wait.
Right? I think this might even class up
"The Ballad of the Uncircumcised Man."
Phoebe..
maybe I wasn't clear before.
I really love listening
to your music here.
But my restaurant,
it's sort of an upscale place.
Right, yeah, okay. I'll ask the butler
to fetch my diamonds out of the vault.
Phoebe, it's not what you wear.
It's sort of your songs.
I just don't think you should play
at the restaurant anymore.
Okay. Fine, I'll just..
I'll take the hat back.
There.
Hey, so, you guys, the funniest
thing happened at work the..
My songs aren't good enough
for your restaurant?
Okay, we're still on that.
- I didn't say they weren't good enough.
- Then what's wrong with them?
What, they don't go with your
tiny portions of pretentious food?
- Tiny portions?
- Yeah, well, "Excuse me.
I ordered the smoked salmon appetizer,
but I can't see it. I can't see it."
- Phoebe, it's not about quantity.
- Well, it's not about quality.
Oh, really?
You wanna talk about quality?
Have you ever heard of a "key"?
It's what some people sing in.
Well, at least all my songs
don't taste like garlic.
Yeah, there are other
ingredients, Monica.
So that's what we're doing.
When I'm in a coffeehouse bopping
along to one of your songs..
I'm wearing earplugs.
Earplugs or cloves of garlic?
You know what?
I take back what I said before.
Keep playing at the restaurant, because
with your music driving people inside..
my bar sales
have gone up like crazy.
What are people having,
the garlic martini?
So you wanna hear my work story?
I'll save it.
Here's your bill.
We hope you enjoyed your stay.
Oh, we did.
And you still have all your lamps.
- I didn't factor in the room tax.
- Dude, don't worry about it.
I found an unattended maid's cart.
We're way ahead of the game.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
There's something new in the bowl.
- Look, we have enough. Just walk away.
- No, but I want the pine cones.
- There's a forest right outside.
- It's not the same.
- No, look. She's gonna see us.
- No, she won't. I'm sly.
Okay, go quick.
Thank you for a delightful stay.
My maple candy!
It's just you. I thought someone was
swinging a bag of cats against the wall.
You'd better get back in that kitchen.
The garlic's not gonna overuse itself.
- Okay, you have to stop playing now.
- Why?
The only person my playing
is bothering is you.
- Oh, yeah? Let's settle this. Come on.
- Get your garlic peelers off me.
Excuse me? Excuse me?
Hi, I'm Monica Geller.
I'm the head chef here.
Okay, I was actually expecting
a little applause there, but whatever.
Quick question.
By a show of hands..
how many of you were bothered
by this woman's singing outside?
Okay, okay. Well, I have a question.
You can put your hand down.
You made your point earlier
when you spit in my guitar case.
Okay, okay. How many of you
enjoyed the music outside?
Let me ask you this question.
How many thought the music was fine..
but not in keeping with the tone
of the restaurant?
Okay, well, who identified this restaurant's
tone as "pretentious-comma-garlicky"?
Okay, who thinks the food is delicious
and a little pretension never hurt anyone?
Okay, well, all right, who thinks
the food is fine, the music was fine..
but your evening was ruined
by this incessant poll-taking?
Excuse us.
All right, here's a question.
Who was so worried about
her restaurant being fancy..
that she made a big deal about
her friend playing her music..
and feels really bad about it now?
Well, who was so stupid
and stubborn..
that she lashed out
against her friend's cooking..
which she actually thinks
is pretty great?
- I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry too.
Hey, you wanna stick around
and I'll whip you up some dinner?
Yeah, as long as it's free.
The food here is ridiculously overpr..
Who hopes the hand-raising thing is still
cute enough that you won't hate me?
- Hey.
Joey, do you have peanut butter
on the back of your head?
Oh, man. I thought I got it all.
How..?
How?
I was making a peanut butter
smoothie, right?
I couldn't find this little plastic thingy
that goes in the top of the blender.
And I thought, "Well, you know,
how important can that be?" Right?
Turns out, very.
Wow, definitely just Drake.
- What?
- How's it going with Drake?
- I don't think it's going very well.
- What?
That scene I saw was so good.
Well, I'm feeling really insecure
about the one we're shooting tomorrow.
Is this that thing you do when you say
you're bad so I'll give you a compliment?
A little.
No, I really am worried. I have to make it
convincing that I'm in love with Olivia.
- So?
- So I've never played that.
Oh, honey, it can't be that hard.
I mean, you've been in love before.
Well, just once..
with you.
Okay. Well, this could be
a little awkward.
I'm just gonna blow past it.
Well, look, can't you just use
that method-actor thing..
where you use your real-life memories
to help you in your performance?
What the hell are you talking about?
All right, look, just try to remember
how you felt when you were in love..
and think about that
when you're playing the scene.
Okay. Yeah, I think I can do that.
Yeah. Okay, there's this
party scene coming up.
And Olivia and her husband are there..
and all Drake wants to do is
grab her and kiss her, but he can't.
That makes me think about those times
I wanted to grab you and kiss you..
but you didn't know, so I would
just pretend everything was cool..
but really it was killing me.
Joey, you never
talked about that before.
Hey, you know what else I could use?
There's this scene where Drake
sneaks into Olivia's bedroom..
and she doesn't know he's there,
which never happened with us.
I mean, he knows he shouldn't be there,
but he just wants to look at her.
You know?
And I remember all those mornings
before you even put on your makeup..
when I would think to myself,
"My God, she is beautiful."
And it hurt so much because
I knew I could never tell you.
But it was worth it just to be there
looking at you.
Thanks, dude. This is great!
I got you something from Vermont.
Besides tampons and salt?
Oh, my God.
Maple candy. That's so sweet of you.
That's weird, it's empty.
Hi, you guys. What's going on?
You guys wanna hang out or..?
Do you guys hear a buzzing?